# Shabd Veyyakula

Tracy, California, United States



linkedin.com/in/shabd-veyyakula-3b879a195



veyyakulashabd@gmail.com



**&** 209 627 7732

## Summary

I am a 15-year old student attending Mountain House High School. I enjoy developing projects in my free time and I aspire of being an Entrepreneur. I enjoy learning new things that have allowed me to create amazing projects in the past. I hope to create even more amazing projects in the future!

## Experience



#### Digital Equity Fellow With Pilot City and Congresswoman Barbara Lee

PilotCity

Jun 2020 - Present (1 month +)

A cyber-physical internship, fellowship, and entrepreneurship program for high school and college students to prototype, pilot, and productize solutions.



## Coding Intern for PilotCity

PilotCity

Jun 2020 - Present (1 month +)

Learning and Developing frontend, backend and data analysis projects for the PilotCity platform



# Xeon Developers

Xeon Developers

Oct 2019 - May 2020 (8 months)

#### Education



#### Mountain House High School

currently attending high school, Computer Science 2018 - 2022





### San Joaquin Delta College

English/History

2018 - 2022

Took US History as well as Worl History at Delta College while attending Mountain House High Shcool. As for English, I am currently taking Language (ENG1A)

#### **Honors & Awards**



#### **Teen Tech SanFrancisco (1st Place)** - Teen Tech SanFrancisco

Oct 2019

First place at Teen Tech SF 2019 Hackathon. We created a Service for students at school to alert everyone in their school if a school shooter is seen or any other suspicious threat.



#### Atoms and Bits (Second Place) - Atoms and Bits

Nov 2019

2nd place at Atoms and Bits hackathon. We created a project called ParCar which helped with reserving parking spaces. We won Fit Bits.

## ■ Global Youth Summit

Dec 2019

We pitched our project to an audience and were live streamed to Teen Tech audiences around the world.

# **SRC Hacks(Best App)** - SRC Hacks

Feb 2020

At SRC hacks we won the award best App. We created a service for any company to hire regular people to deliver their products

# ■ LA Hacks (Honorable Mention) - UCLA

Mar 2020

At LA Hacks, we created a social media service for developers to pitch their idea and find members to collaborate with.

## ☐ Crypto Hacks (1st Place) - Crypto Hacks

Feb 2020

At Crypto Hacks we created an app to allow someone to host an event to gain members who can get community service hours.

#### **Skills**

Web Development • Flutter • HTML5 • JavaScript • Bootstrap • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • jQuery • Python (Programming Language) • Learn New Software Quickly • Oboe